Thank you for watching!
Good morning.
It's not good morning.
Say good morning.
Good morning.
Today's project is...
We gave you a present before.
Kikami-san came up with this song.
That's it?
What?
Which one is Kikami-san?
Fujitani-san is funny.
She is the funniest.
If you watch her funny video everyday,
you can easily tell which one is her
and which one is not.
I see.
So, we asked you to think of 8 jokes.
When you do that,
you can also do what other people
think.
You can ask each other which one is
her.
You can play a game with Kikami-san and
Hazuki-san.
The loser will tell the joke that
Fujitani-san came up with.
Wait.
What did you say?
I have to do what Miyu-san came up
with.
I can't lose.
You will tell the joke at the end.
I thought of that too.
If I slip, it will be Miyu's fault.
It's okay.
I can't laugh at the editing.
The video may end.
Wait.
I don't want to.
So, let's have Fujitani-san prepare the
joke.
Let's do it.
Go!
The first joke.
Please.
This is the first one.
The one you just did is the first one.
3, 4, Action!
Takecopter!
Let's go home!
OK, that's it.
Hitomi and Kabuki.
Whichever one is mine, it's Fujitami's.
Whichever one knows which one is mine.
Wait a minute.
Takecopter, I want to see it again.
You want to see it again?
Let's go.
Takecopter!
What's wrong?
That's good.
I've been doing my hair like a pony for
this.
Which one is mine?
I've decided.
Let's start with Kabuki.
The joke that Miyu made is Takecopter.
I also chose Takecopter.
Let's have Fujitami
do the joke again.
Takecopter, come here.
Fujitami!
Takecopter was funny.
By the way,
this is Shinju.
It's funny.
Miyu's face was funny.
Shinju and Ecchan,
you did a joke that Miyu made.
Thank you.
It was funny.
I'm sad.
It's just a practice.
Let's move on to the second question.
We are ready. Let's go to the second
question.
Tsuki and Suponpon
What does that mean?
It's a bunny, right?
Suponpon
I
will do it
, which one is it?
It's the same thing I
love, I don't know which one is
I don't know how many times I've seen
this.
I've decided.
The gag that Miyu thought of is a gun
gag.
I also don't know how many times I've
seen this.
The correct answer is...
Miyu got the correct answer.
I'm glad.
What is Tsukitosuponpon?
It's a word that means the moon and the
moon.
Is there a word called Tsukitosuponpon?
No.
There is a word called Tsukitosupon.
I didn't think of that.
The third question.
This is fun.
My company is lonely.
Please.
Can you hear my stomach?
She is excited.
This is it.
Is it funny?
She is laughing.
I'll do it.
Please.
I'm going to do it.
I've decided.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
But I've decided.
The gag that Miyu came up with is ZO.
I've decided.
It seems that you like it, so let's
have you do the correct gag again.
ZO!
The one I did?
Yes.
Thank you.
You're very confident.
Who came up with that?
Waida.
It's funny.
He did it, but I thought it was funny.
I want to see it.
Let's have him do it again.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please do the fourth one.
Let's take a break.
I knew it.
Please do the fifth one.
Hinoyoji!
T!
I didn't write anything on T.
Which one is it?
Let's take a break.
I knew it!
I can't believe it!
I made up my mind.
The gag that Miyu came up with is...
T!
Mr.
I got it for the first time.
The answer is...
T!
I did it!
By the way, this E-Star is...
Captain!
That's funny!
You are leading with 4 questions.
I have 4 more questions.
Yes, you do.
Please prepare for the 5th question.
Senta-kun!
I'm ready.
Soshina!
Which one is it?
It's big.
I'm so excited.
Have you decided?
Yes.
The one you thought is Senta-kun.
I'll choose Soshina.
Please announce the answer.
Senta-kun!
By the way, Soshina is...
Wakarin!
That's funny.
It's so funny.
She sent me a message.
She wrote Wara-Wara-Wara at the end.
Please prepare for the 6th question.
Question 6
Hello?
Yesterday?
It was fun.
Where do you want to have lunch
tomorrow?
What?
There?
I knew it.
By the way, who are you?
I'm Toraemon.
What?
It's funny.
Which one is better?
Toraemon.
I think it's funny.
I've decided.
I'm Toraemon.
Toraemon.
Correct.
I'm getting it.
You are?
It's funny.
By the way, this is Mon-chan.
I think she's doing it.
I think so.
I'll ask Mon-chan.
Please get ready for the 7th question.
Deuf
I beg you
My eyes are dry.
Spit!
Please be careful of the atmosphere.
Clap!
I know the answer.
Which one is it?
I thought about it.
Clap!
The answer is...
You are doing it wrong.
You are doing it well.
This is Karen.
It's funny.
I made a mistake.
I thought it was Yui.
It's not.
I made a mistake.
It's funny.
The last question.
If you continue,
Kazuki has 6 points.
Hitomi has 4 points.
If you don't get more than 3 points,
Hitomi can't win.
But, you can't get more than 3 points.
You can do one of the jokes you have
done so far.
I'll do it.
Imparen is the best.
That's not what I meant.
You just did it.
Really?
Which one is good?
I'll do it.
I can do it.
I'll bend here.
I'll do it.
It's funny.
I'm glad.
I like Doraemon.
Do you like Doraemon?
I'm glad.
It was funny.
You showed us your joke.
Azuki, are you okay with the last
question?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
Get ready for the last question.
The last question.
Post-it.
Shibushi's heart is beating fast.
Which one is it?
It's difficult.
Doraemon.
Post-it.
Good.
Which one do you want?
Let's do it again.
Which one?
I'll do it.
Shut up!
Shimo shimo, dokidoki!
I made it!
What is the joke that Miyu-chan came up
with?
Shimo shimo, dokidoki!
I'll be the same.
I think it's better to be different.
It's a birthday cake!
The last question. Please recreate the
correct gag.
th
why
My mom!
It was so fun!
I'm glad.
I was bleeding.
Really?
I'm glad.
You were bleeding.
It was the opposite.
It was fun.
So, we have finished the presentation.
The final score is 3.
Kazuki got 6.
Hitomi got 7.
The lucky Fujitani King is Hitomi.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Don't go.
I won't.
Thank you.
So, the loser Kazuki will be judged by
Fujitani King.
We will show you the last scene of
Tokyo Invader.
I'm glad.
This video will be finished with this
scene.
I'm glad.
I'm sure.
Please sit in the middle.
I will play the penalty game.
The last song of Tachikawa Stage Garden
Encore.
The song is called Outro.
I did it.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!